well I hope you enjoyed that sounded
好吧，我希望你喜欢那听起来
like you did the world has lots of
像你一样，这个世界有很多
theories about what's going on in the
有关在发生了什么理论
inside of people in that video I counted
我认为那个视频中 的人在 里面
six different things that were said
说了六件不同的事情
about Katherine poor Katherine with all
关于凯瑟琳可怜的凯瑟琳与所有人
of her problems here's one of the things
她的问题， 这里的事情之一
she was given the label of
她被赋予了标签
claustrophobic
幽闭恐惧症
another thing that she said is I'm
她说的另一件事是我
compelled and then Bob Newhart said on
迫使Bob Newhart说道
this one she said my horoscope said and
这一个她说我的星座说和
he said we definitely don't go there she
他说我们绝对不会去她那里
said my mother called me fatty she said
她妈妈说我母亲叫我肥胖
this has been with me from childhood and
从小就和 我在一起
then one well we're all laughing it's
那么一口井我们都笑了
hard to hear she said I had this dream
很难听到她说我有这个梦想
and he said we definitely don't go there
他说，我们绝对不会去那里
the world has hundreds of theories and
世界上有数百种理论和理论
just think with me for a moment about
只是觉得与我 有关时刻
what's going on with people and what's
这是怎么回事的人，什么是
causing their problems there's all kinds
导致他们的问题各种各样
of environment theories my father didn't
我父亲没有的环境理论
love me enough or there's wounded inner
爱我， 或者内心受伤
child theories and then there's the
儿童理论，然后有
medical theories it's my brain and the
医学理论这是我的大脑和
chemical imbalances in my brain others
其他人的化学不平衡
would say it's your low self esteem
会说这是你的低自尊
that's why you have the problems that
这就是你遇到问题的原因
you do there's personality theories
你做那里的人格理论
you're a type-a that's why you are like
你是一个类型 - 这就是你喜欢的原因
you are there are literally hundreds of
你有几百个
theories that are operating in the world
在世界上运作的理论
right now as to why humans do the things
现在为什么人类会做这些事情
that they do so what we're gonna do here
他们这样做我们将在这里做什么
for the time that we have is look at
在我们看到的时间
what the Bible says about human
圣经对人类所说的话
motivation what's going on in the heart
动机内心正在发生什么
this is an incredibly important topic
这是一个非常重要的话题
and let me just give you one statistic
让我给你一个统计数据
this word heart both in the Old
这个词心脏都在旧
Testament New Testament together
遗嘱新约在一起
combined is used over 1,000 times
合并使用超过1,000次
so anytime I think you'd agree with me
所以任何时候我认为你都同意我的观点
anytime that the Bible uses a word over
任何时候圣经使用一个词
a thousand times don't you think it
千万次你不觉得
would be important for us to study it so
这对我们来说非常重要
we're gonna look just for a few minutes
我们只会看几分钟
here in our time together of what does
在这里，我们在一起的时间
the Bible mean by the word heart and
圣经用这个词的意思是心脏和
we're gonna do some studying together on
我们要一起做一些学习
that topic you have a diagram in your
这个话题你 有一个图你
notes that we lovingly call the three
注意到我们亲切地称这三个人
trees diagram and we're gonna test your
树图，我们要测试你的
coordination here I need you to pull out
在这里协调我需要你退出
that diagram and be filling in your
那个图表并填写你的
outline at the same time you think you
在你认为你的同时勾勒出大纲
can handle that on a Friday evening so
可以处理在周五晚上这样
you're gonna be filling in the outline
你要填写大纲
and filling in the three trees diagram
并填写三棵树图
so you'll have to be flipping back and
所以你必须要退回去
forth and I'm gonna do two things at
我将做两件事
once here just to test my coordination
曾经在这里只是为了测试我的协调
and yours we're gonna be looking at this
和我们要去寻找 这个 你
diagram and filling in point two of your
图表并填写您的第二点
outline that talks about some basic
谈论一些基本的概述
Bible passages that have to do with the
圣经段落有与做
heart I'll come back to the diagram in a
我将回到图中
moment but let's look at mark chapter
那一刻，但让我们来看看标记章节
seven and while you're turning to mark
七，当你转向标记时
chapter seven just to save us a little
第七章只是为了拯救我们一点
time I'm going to quote the following to
一次我要去报价如下，以
proverbs 4:23 and Jeremiah 17:9 people
箴言4:23和耶利米书17：9
that do word studies and put together
做单词研究和拼凑
what the Bible has to say about these
圣经对这些有什么看法
topics say that for a biblical
主题说，对于圣经
anthropology the most important word is
人类学最重要的词是
the word heart now if someone would have
如果有人愿意的话， 现在就说出这个词
asked me years ago what's the most
几年前我问过什么是最重要的
important word biblically for the inner
圣经为内心而言的重要词汇
person I wouldn't have said heart I
我不会说我的心
would have said the word soul but the
本来会说灵魂这个词而不是
word heart is used hundreds of times
单词心脏使用了数百次
more than than what the Bible uses the
比圣经使用的更多
word soul let's just take a peek at some
单词灵魂让我们看看一些
of these you're in mark 7 let me quote
这些你在标记7中让我引用
proverbs 4:23 great verse says guard
箴言4:23 伟大的经文说守卫
your heart with all diligence for from
从尽心尽力的心
it flow the issues of life
它流动着生活的问题
or a famous one Jeremiah 17:9 the heart
还是着名的耶利米书17：9
is deceitful and desperately wicked who
是欺骗和绝望的邪恶谁
can know it I hope what will happen with
可以知道我希望会发生什么
this brief presentation is that heart
这个简短的介绍就是那个心
verses are just going to start popping
经文刚刚开始流行
out of the pages of scripture as we
从圣经的页面 ，因为我们的
think about why do humans do the things
想想为什么人类会这样做
that they do now the main passage I'd
他们现在做的主要通道是我
like for us to be in for just a few
喜欢我们只是为了几个
minutes is mark chapter 7 and I'm going
分钟是第7章，我要去了
to begin reading with verse 21 and as
开始阅读第21节和作为
you might guess this is the Lord talking
你可能会猜到这是主在说话
to the Pharisees and when you think
法利赛人和你想的时候
Pharisee I know the kind of words that
法利赛人我知道之类的词语是
come to my mind when I think Pharisee
当我想到法利赛人时，我想到了
and they're probably in your mind - we
他们可能在你的脑海里 - 我们
think legalist we think self-righteous
我们认为法律主义者认为自以为是
we think hypocrite but I would like to
我们认为伪君子，但我想
propose to you just for a moment to
提议给你一点时间
think about the Pharisees and as I've
想想法利赛人和我一样
studied a little bit about the Pharisees
研究了法利赛人的一点点
I have often thought of them as the
我经常把它们当成了
pastor's dream team that sounds strange
牧师的梦之队听起来很奇怪
doesn't it now think about it for a
没有它现在想想了
moment they're in church every time the
那一刻他们每次都在教堂里
doors are open they are faithfully
门是开放的，他们是忠实的
studying their Bibles they are
研究他们的圣经
meticulous about their Bible study they
他们对圣经​​的研究一丝不苟
give very faithfully they are very
非常忠实地给予他们非常
faithful about their giving and when you
忠实于他们的奉献和你的时间
think about the Pharisees that way is
想想法利 赛人说的方法是
the most religious group of people at
最宗教的一群人
their time you wonder why in the world
他们想知道为什么在这个世界上
did the Lord pick on these people so
主如何选择这些人
much well we get a hint of that in mark
很好，我们在商标中得到了一丝暗示
chapter 7 beginning with verse 21 he
与第21节开始的第7章，他
says this for from within out of the
从内到外说这个
heart of men proceed the evil thoughts
人的心脏进行邪恶的思想
you wonder where do your evil thoughts
你想知道你的邪恶想法在哪里
come from the Lord says it's the heart
来自主说它的心脏
fornications theft starts in the heart
fornications盗窃始于心脏
murder starts in the heart adultery the
谋杀开始在心脏通奸
heart this next phrase is interesting
心脏这下一个短语很有意思
because it has both an outward and an
因为它有向外和向外
inward dynamic deeds outward of coveting
令人垂涎的内向动力
inward
向内的
originated in the heart wickedness as
起源于心中的邪恶
well as deceit sensuality envy slander
以及欺骗性感嫉妒诽谤
pride in foolishness all these evil
骄傲愚蠢所有这些邪恶
things proceed from within and defile
事物从内部发展并玷污
the man look a little bit earlier in the
男人看起来早一点
chapter the Lord is quoting a famous
主章引用了一位名人
verse from Isaiah in verse 6 and he said
他在第6节中讲述了以赛亚的经文
rightly did Isaiah prophesy of you
以赛亚对你的预言是正确的
hypocrites as it is written this people
伪君子， 因为这是写这个人
honors me with their lips but their
用他们的嘴唇来表达我的荣誉
heart is far away from me in vain do
心脏是远离我也是枉然
they worship Me teaching as doctrines
他们崇拜我教导作为教义
the precepts of men I brought a one of
男人的戒律我带了一个
my favorite toys with me tonight my
今晚我和我最喜欢的玩具
laser pointer so I can point out some
激光指针所以我可以指出一些
various things we want to talk about
我们想谈的各种事情
what does the Bible mean about this
圣经对此有何意义
thing called the heart and let's just
被称为心脏的东西，让我们只是
start filling in this diagram let's
开始填写这个图表让我们
start up here and we're gonna be working
从这里开始，我们将要工作
our way clockwise around the diagram
我们沿着图表顺时针方向
let's start with the pressure up at the
让我们从压力上开始吧
top our counsel ease come to us because
最重要的是我们的忠告来到我们身边，因为
they're having problems they're
他们有他们的问题
experiencing the pressures of life think
经历生活压力的思考
of that as heat what's causing the heat
那是因为热量引起的热量
what's causing the pressure and if you
是什么导致了压力，如果你
think of biblical words for pressure one
想到圣经中的压力之一
of the words that would come to mind
那会浮现在脑海中的话
would be trials the circumstances of
将审判的情况
life the things that are putting
生活中的东西
pressure on us we want to find out why
对我们施加压力我们想找出原因
is it that this person with this
是这个人这个
pressure is responding this way and we
压力正在以这种方式回应我们
call this the three trees diagram
叫这三棵树图
because of this tree this tree which is
因为此树此树是的
central and then this tree the bad fruit
中央然后这棵树坏果子
tree and the good fruit tree and the
树和好果树和树
difference that Christ makes because of
基督所造的差异是因为
the gospel in our lives even if the
我们生活中的福音即使是
pressure of life never changes so let's
生活的压力永远不会改变所以让我们
be realistic here let's take some
在这里现实让我们采取一些
typical pressure for Los Angeles I was
洛杉矶的典型压力我是
in South Dakota last weekend and I came
上周末在南达科他州，我来了
back on early Monday morning after
早在星期一早上回来之后
seeing miles and miles and miles of open
看到英里，英里和英里的开放
plains and
平原和
South Dakota and I come back and land at
南达科他州和我回来登陆
Burbank Airport and see miles and miles
伯班克机场，看英里和英里
and miles of cars let's talk about
和几英里的汽车让我们谈谈
traffic for a moment causing pressure in
交通片刻造成压力
our lives how do we respond to the
我们的生活，我们如何来应对的
pressure of traffic the heat the trial
交通压力的热量试验
the circumstances of pressure here on
的压力在这里的情况
the bad fruit tree notice the dotted
坏果树注意点缀
line your diagram I don't believe has
排除你的图表我不相信
that dotted line you can draw that diet
该虚线可以得出，饮食
and dotted line but make sure you draw
和虚线，但要确保你画
it precisely that it's going right
它恰恰是正确的
across the top of the heart because what
因为什么，穿过心脏的顶部
we're trying to do is divide what the
我们要做的就是划分什么
Bible talks about as the inner person
圣经谈论作为内在的人
from the outer person or the root system
来自外部人或根系
of our life from the fruit system in our
我们生活中的水果系统
life or the soul from the body inner
生命或灵魂来自身体内心
person outer person so what might be
那个人外面所以可能是什么
going on with the traffic well there
继续那里的交通很好
might be sweaty palms there might be
可能是手心出汗可能有
angry gestures and if I was using this
愤怒的姿势，如果我使用这个
to take notes with the counsel II and
与律师II和。做笔记
I'm finding out what's causing the
我发现了导致这种情况的原因
pressure in my counsel 'is life I would
我的忠告中的压力是我的生命
be drawing on the bad fruit tree all of
全都画在坏果树上
the bad fruit the outer person stuff
外面的人的坏果子
that's coming out but I want to help my
那是出来但我想帮助我
counsel II understand the root system
律师II了解根系
where is this coming from in their inner
这来自于他们的内心
person and that's the main topic for
人，这对主要议题
this session which is the theme of what
本届会议的主题是什么
the Bible calls the heart so all kinds
圣经把各种各样的心称为心
of things can come out right when
东西可以出来权当
there's traffic
有交通
the thought life anger maybe fear etc
思想生活的愤怒可能是恐惧等
all kinds of bad fruit could be coming
各种糟糕的果实都可能来临
out in the person's life that's
在这个人的生命中
experiencing that that pressure in the
经历那种压力
person's life up here at the top right
人在右上角的生活
we have a biblical principle of sowing
我们有一个圣经的播种原则
and reaping this is not just the
并且收获这不仅仅是
biblical principle of what I sow is what
我所播种的圣经原则是什么
I'm going to reap that's convicting
我要收获那个有罪的人
enough right then what I'm going to sow
足够正确的，然后我什么都播种
is what I reap basically the whole book
是我收获基本上整本书
of Proverbs is based on that principle
箴言是基于这个原则
my son
我的儿子
if you
如果你
this direction you're gonna get this in
这个方向你会得到这个
your life but my son if you go this way
如果你这样走，你的生活，但我的儿子
you're gonna get this in your life the
你会在生活中得到这个
principle of sowing and reaping but
播种和收割的原则但是
sowing and reaping also has the
播种和收割也有
implication with it of habits in our
它与我们的习惯有关
lives i sow and i read i sow and i read
生活我播种，我读我播种，我读
i sow and i reap and a person can just
我播种，我收获，一个人可以
get stuck on this side of the diagram
陷在图的这一边
with the pressures of life I keep sowing
随着生活的压力，我一直在播种
and reaping sowing and reaping sowing
并收获播种和收获播种
and reaping and one of the things that
和收获和其中一件事
you need to just start letting sink in
你需要刚开始让水槽
for this presentation is that those
对于这个演示文稿是那些
habit patterns are coming from something
习惯模式来自于某种东西
deeper in my inner person that the Bible
在我内心的人更深的圣经
talks about over a thousand times and
谈论了一千多次
it's this idea of the heart what we want
这就是我们想要的内心
to see is that by the power of the
看到的是，通过对电源
gospel let me take you to another
福音让我把你带到另一个
passage Isaiah 61 please turn there if
通过以赛亚书61请转到那里
you would
你会
Isaiah 61 that the Lord by the power of
以赛亚书61章是耶和华所赐的力量
the gospel wants to set us free he says
他说 ，福音希望让我们自由
things like this wonderful things that
像这样美妙的东西
our Lord promises John 8:32
我们的主应许约翰福音8:32
you will know the truth and the truth
你会知道真相和真相
will set you free he makes it possible
会让你自由他让它成为可能
so that change happens so that I don't
所以改变发生，所以我不这样做
have to keep sowing and reaping sowing
必须继续播种和收割播种
and reaping on this side even if the
并且即使在这方面也能收获
pressure the circumstances of my life
压力我的生活环境
don't change I can learn sowing and
不要改变我可以学习播种和
reaping coming from a heart that
收获来自一颗心
produces good fruit in my life my life
好果子在我的生活我的生活
instead of bad fruit in my life listen
而不是我生命中的坏水果听
to Isaiah 61 I just absolutely love
以赛亚书61我非常喜欢
these verses I'm gonna read isaiah 61:1
这些经文我将读到以赛亚书61：1
and then the first part of verse 2 and
然后是第2节和第2节的第一部分
this is the just the beauty of the
这是 对正义的美丽
gospel of what we're promising people
我们有希望的人的 福音
that they don't have to be stuck the
他们不必被困住了
Spirit of the Lord God is upon me this
主的灵在我身上
is the Messiah talking because the Lord
是弥赛亚说话，因为主
has anointed me he's the Messiah The
已经膏了我他是弥赛亚的
Anointed One it's the same word for
受膏者它是同一个词
Christ the Christos the Anointed One to
基督克里斯托受膏者到
bring the good
带来好处
Jews and what's our word for that gospel
犹太人和我们对福音的说法是什么
to the afflicted he has sent me to bind
他把我送到了受 约束的地方
up the brokenhearted to proclaim Liberty
心碎的人宣布自由
to captives freedom to prisoners and
俘虏和囚犯的自由
this is wonderful to proclaim grace the
宣扬恩典是非常好的
favorable year of the Lord the
主的有利年份
centrality of the gospel the Lord didn't
主所没有的福音的中心地位
just save me to give me an insurance
救救我给我一个保险
ticket so that I can go to heaven
票让我可以去天堂
someday now praise God for that that he
总有一天，因为他而赞美上帝
did but the gospel is much more than
但是，福音远不止于此
that he saves us to change us in
他节省了我们改变我们
Christ's likeness even if the
即使是基督的样式
circumstances don't change I can learn
情况不改变我可以学习
to respond differently to the same
以不同的方式响应相同
pressure traffic or whatever the
压力交通或其他什么
pressure is in life I can respond my
生活中的压力我可以回应我
route system can change my inner person
路线系统可以改变我的内心
can change because of the power of the
可以因为力量而改变
gospel so that good fruit comes out
福音使好果子出来
isn't that good news that's the power of
并不是那个有力量的好消息
the gospel to change lives and then I
改变生活的福音然后我
can learn new habit patterns and instead
可以学习新的习惯模式
of sowing and reaping on this side
在这一边播种和收割
through progressive sanctification I can
通过渐进的成圣，我可以
learn to grow and change sowing and
学会种植和改变播种和播种
reaping on this side now let's go back
收获这边现在，让我们 回到
to our I'll finish filling in the
我们将完成填写
diagram you wouldn't like me if I didn't
如果我没有，你会不会喜欢我的图表
fill in the diagram right especially all
特别是所有人都填写图表
the control freaks here you got to have
控制狂在这里你必须拥有
all the blanks filled in here we go let
填好的所有空白我们都去了
me fill it the rest of this in I think
在我想，我填写其余部分
you even have a blank that I don't have
你甚至有一个我没有的空白
my diagram right down here do you have a
我的图表就在这里你有一个
blank right at the bottom okay
在底部空白没问题
right at the bottom of the cross you
就在十字架底部你
should write these words the gospel and
应该把这些话写成福音和
all its implications you have that very
你所拥有的所有影响
good so the gospel and all of its
好的福音和所有 的福音
implications I like saying that rather
影响我喜欢说，而
than just the gospel because the gospel
不仅仅是福音，因为福音
is not just the good news that you can
你不仅可以获得好消息
be saved to go to heaven someday the
有一天会被救到天堂去
gospel is also all kinds of implications
福音也是各种含义
of what the Lord wants to do in your
主想要做什么
life now to change you to help you grow
生活现在改变你，帮助你成长
and change the Lord didn't leave you
改变主没有离开你
stuck so that you're on your own look at
陷入困境让你自己看看
the resources that he's given you
他给你的资源
grow and change and your counsel II
成长和变化以及你的忠告II
there are over sixty one anothers in the
在这里有超过六十一个人
New Testament that were made for
为新约而制作的新约
relationship and were made to come
关系，并成为来
alongside one another to help one
彼此并肩帮助
another grow in relationship with the
另一个与...的关系增长
Lord
主
Wayne used this passage your word have I
韦恩用这句话你的话我
treasured or hidden my heart that I may
珍惜或隐藏我的心，我可能
not sin against you God not only has
不是犯了罪， 上帝不仅有
given us the body of Christ he's given
给了我们基督的身体， 他给了我们
us the Living Word of God and then
我们是上帝的生命之道然后
Galatians 4:6 says he has put his Holy
加拉太书4：6说他已经把他的圣洁
Spirit guess where in your heart whereby
灵猜测凡在你的心脏，其中
we cry Abba Father in relationship with
我们和Abba 父亲一起哭泣
the Lord
主
incredible resources that the Lord has
主拥有的令人难以置信的资源
given us so we're not on our own to kind
给了我们，所以我们不能靠自己的实力去做
of tough it out to try to grow and
努力实现成长
change let's keep going and think about
改变让我们继续思考
some definitions of the word heart what
心脏这个词的一些定义是什么
is the heart biblical we're gonna look
是我们要看的心脏圣经
at the Old Testament word here the Old
在旧约圣经中，这里是古老的
Testament word if you want to put it in
遗嘱单词，如果你想把它放入
your notes as Ellie V LAIV and brown
你的笔记是Ellie V LAIV和棕色
driver and Briggs gas Aeneas lexicon
司机和布里格斯燃气埃涅阿斯词典
that's just a fancy word for a Hebrew a
这只是一个希伯来文看中字
dictionary says this is what the heart
字典说这是什么心脏
is it's your inner person in contrast to
相比之下，这是你的内心
the outer the inner person with you or
内在的人与你或
think of the counseling implications
想一想咨询的意义
it's mind affections and will or we
这是心灵的感情和意志或我们
might say mind emotions and we'll even
可能会说心情， 我们甚至会
though the word affections here is
虽然这里的感情这个词是
different than emotions are a little bit
比情绪不同的是一点点
different than emotions so mind
比情绪，以不同的心态
affections and we'll reveal the heart in
感情， 我们将揭示内心
your notes you also have a series of
你的笔记你也有一系列
questions called drawing out the
问题称为抽出
purposes of the heart questions that's
心脏的目的是问题
back where the diagram was those
回到图表那里
questions revolve around these
问题围绕这些问题展开
definitions I want to ask my counsel
定义我想问我的律师
leaks questions about their thought
泄漏有关他们思想的问题
processes their decision making that's
处理他们的决策 这是
their will why do they make the
他们为什么会这样做
decisions that they do and their
他们做的决定和他们的
emotions realizing that all three of
情绪意识到，所有三个
those things biblically the Lord says
耶和华如圣经所说的那些事
that is your heart your mind your
这是你的心灵你的心
emotions
情绪
and your will number four says it's
而你的遗嘱数字就是四分之一
specific reference to the inclinations
具体提到倾向
why am i inclined a certain way
为什么我倾向于某种方式
resolutions and determinations of the
的决议和决定
will it's a synonym for the word
它会是这个词的同义词吗？
conscience and then these last two I
良心，然后这最后两个我
want to slow John down just a little bit
想慢下来约翰只是一点点
and think about the counseling
并考虑咨询
implications here for our our counsel
对我们的律师的影响
ease in our own lives they're saying
他们说，在我们自己的生活中轻松自如
that all of these hundreds and hundreds
所有这些数以百计
of references when the Scriptures use
圣经使用时的引用
the word heart it has to do with your
它与你的心脏有关
appetites what are you hungry for and
胃口渴望你渴望和
we're using this metaphorically of
我们正在使用这个比喻
course
课程
what are you hungry for let me just
你有什么渴望让我公正的
start throwing out some suggestions some
开始抛出一些建议
people seem really hungry for approval I
人们似乎 批准我真的饿了
have to have people happy with me all
必须让人们满意我
the time or some people I'm really
时间或某些人我真的
hungry I just have this appetite to keep
饥饿我只是有这种胃口要保持
my life under control I've got to be
我的生活在掌控之中我必须成为
organized those are the types of themes
组织这些是主题的类型
that I'm looking for in my counsel II I
我正在寻找我的律师III
believe that the heart when the
相信心里的时候
scripture talks about the heart being
经文讲述了心灵的存在
what motivates us on the inside that the
什么激励我们在内心的那个
heart is what drives me the heart is
心是驱动我的心
what is my world revolving around and
什么是我的世界旋转和
often you find it's those type of themes
通常你会发现它是那种主题
my life revolves around keeping people
我的生活围绕着人们
happy my life revolves around keeping my
幸福我的生活围绕着保持我的生活
life under control
生活在掌控之中
my life revolves around being as
我的生活围绕着如同
comfortable as possible and I'm gonna
尽可能舒服，我会
give you a list of suggested themes and
给你一个建议的主题和列表
I hope you are starting to get the
我希望你开始得到了
connection here of why this important is
这里重要的是为什么这么重要
important if this is the root system you
重要的是，如果这是你的根系统
can see why this root system is then
可以看出为什么这个根系统是
producing the fruit that's coming out
生产这是未来出来的水果
under the pressures of life so here's
在生活的压力下，所以这里
why this is important if we don't want
如果我们不想要的话，为什么这很重要
biblical counseling to just be
圣经辅导就是
behaviorist
行为主义
they can just outward we need to deal
他们可以向外我们需要处理
with what's motivating our counsel ease
用什么激励我们的律师放心
on the inside
在里面
remember scripture says of some very
记得经文说的很多
important things about the heart and
关于心脏的重要事情
here might be the most important verse
这可能是最重要的一节
love the Lord your God with all your
用 你所有的 爱，爱你的上帝
heart soul mind and strength the Lord is
主是心灵的灵魂和力量
not just interested in behaviorist ik
不仅仅对行为主义者感兴趣
people he's interested in people who are
人他有兴趣的人谁是
loving him from the inside out
从内到外爱他
from the deepest parts of our being that
从我们最深处那里得到的
we're loving him and that out of that
我们爱他和那个
inward person is coming the outward
内心的人正在向外
actions this next one is really
下一个是真的
important the seat of New Testament
重要的是新约的所在地
lusts and desires let's dwell on that
欲望和欲望让我们纠缠于此
one just a little bit the seat of New
一个只是一点点新的座位
Testament lusts and desires what they're
遗嘱欲望和渴望他们是什么
saying is that the Old Testament word
说是旧约的话
for heart is synonymous to the New
对于新人来说 ，心灵是同义词
Testament idea and the Greek word is
遗嘱和希腊词是
epithelia strong desire now when we
我们现在的上皮强烈欲望
think and we have to stop thinking this
我想，我们不得不停止这样思考
way when we think lust in American
当我们想到美国人的欲望时
culture we read in the New Testament the
文化，我们在新约圣经阅读
word lust we automatically think sex
字欲求我们自动思考性
that is not how the New Testament uses
这不是新约圣经的用法
this word now you're gonna want to stone
这个词现在你要石头了
me possibly when I say this next thing
我可能当我说下一件事
but in the Gospel of Luke guess who this
但在卢克的福音中猜猜是谁
is used of it's actually used of Jesus
使用它实际上是耶稣使用的
you ready to throw Rotten Tomatoes at me
你准备好把腐烂的西红柿扔给我
Luke chapter 22 Jesus says and the
路加第22章耶稣说和
english translators wisely know they
英语翻译明智地知道他们
can't translate lust right you can't say
不能翻译欲望你不能说
that our Lord was lusting but it says in
我们的主渴望，但它说
Luke 22 at the Last Supper I have been
在最后的晚餐上的路加福音22 我去过
strongly desiring to eat this meal with
非常希望吃这顿饭
you it's the exact same word for lust
你是欲望的完全相同的词
what they're saying is that this Old
他们所说的是这个老
Testament idea of llave heart is
遗嘱心中的遗嘱是
equivalent to the New Testament idea of
相当于新约的想法
strong desire strong desire humans are
强烈渴望人类强烈渴望
made with passion and desires when I am
在我的时候充满激情和欲望
counseling someone I am not trying to
咨询我不想尝试的人
get them to kill desire
让他们杀死欲望
I am NOT trying to get them to kill
我不是想让他们杀人
passion praise God that God made us so
激情赞美上帝，上帝创造了我们
that we can be passionate about things
我们可以对事物充满热情
please don't try to kill passion in your
请不要试图杀死你的激情
counsel ease life here's the problem is
律师缓解生活这里的问题是
we get passionate about the wrong things
我们对错误的事情充满热情
we have strong desires about the wrong
我们对错误有强烈的渴望
things instead of the right things I
事情而不是正确的事情我
need to help my counsel ease learn to
需要帮助我的建议轻松学会
have passionate strong desires about the
对...有着强烈的强烈欲望
right things putting it bluntly we don't
正确的事情， 把它说白了，我们不
lust after Christ enough we need to
我们需要足够的基督之后的欲望
learn how to love the Lord our God with
学会如何爱我们的上帝耶和华与
all of our heart soul mind and strength
我们所有的心灵灵魂和力量
some questions to get at the heart
要抓住一些问题
remember the heart has to do with your
记得心脏与你有关
emotions so when do you tend to
情绪所以你什么时候倾向于
experience fear worry or anxiety right
体验恐惧担忧或焦虑的权利
after this outline are those questions
在这个大纲之后是那些问题
14 heart questions drawing out the
提出了14个心脏问题
purposes of the heart I pretty much use
我很常用 的心脏的目的
those 14 questions with virtually all
几乎所有的14个问题
counsel ease and it's one of the ways I
律师轻松，这是我的方式之一
get started in counseling as a way to
在辅导开始，以此来
get get started and as they're filling
开始时，他们正在填补
out those questions when they fill out
出这些问题，当他们填写
those questions for me I look then for
那些问题对我来说，我期待着
patterns I look for repeated words for
模式我寻找重复的单词
repeated ideas I'm true I'm teaching
重复的想法我是真的我在教学
them the three trees diagram draw the
他们三棵树图画了
diagram I draw the diagram for them and
图我绘制了它们的图表
then I might ask a question based upon
然后我可能会问一个基于的问题
what we're studying from God's Word
我们从神的话语中学习什么
about the heart and based upon the way
关于心脏和基于方式
that you're answering your questions
你正在回答你的问题
about the heart what might you call your
关于你可能称之为你的心脏
heart themes there's something really
心脏主题真的有些东西
powerful about a person naming their own
关于一个人命名自己的强大
heart themes rather than you telling
心脏主题，而不是你告诉
them their heart themes I'll do that but
他们的心脏主题我会这样做但是
reluctantly I'd much rather have a
不情愿地我宁愿有一个
person say well you know what I'm coming
人说你知道我要来的
to realize that I'm more of a control
要认识到，我更多的是控制
freak then I thought I was or I'm much
然后，我以为我是，或者我
more of a comfort lover than I thought I
更多的是一个比我想象的舒适爱好者
was wow I'm a people pleaser I never
哇，我是一个让我高兴的人，我永远不会
really under
真的在
stood why I'm so concerned about the
站在我为什么这么关心
approval of people but now I get it
人民的认可，但现在我明白了
that's my heart what's on your mind
那是我心中的想法
first thing in the morning remember or
早上的第一件事就是记得或者
last thing at night or maybe two o'clock
在晚上最后一件事或许两点钟
in the morning when you wake up because
在当你醒来，因为早晨
you can't sleep what's on your mind
你无法入睡你的想法
and are you are there some patterns
你有一些模式吗？
there remember the heart is about the
那里记得心脏是关于
mind where do your eyes drift remember
记住你的眼睛在哪里记忆
the heart is about the will you make a
心是关于你的意志
decision to use your eyes in a certain
决定用你的眼睛
way so why do you look at the things
所以你为什么看看这些东西
that you look at and what is that
你看看，什么是
telling you about your inner motivations
告诉你你的内心动机
in what situations do you struggle with
在什么情况下你会挣扎
anger that's back to the emotions and
愤怒回归情绪和
what why do you make the decision to
什么你为什么做出决定
avoid things that you avoid now let's go
避免你现在放弃的事情
to Hebrews 4:12 a very important heart
希伯来书4:12是一颗非常重要的心
passage and think about Hebrews 4:12 for
通过并思考希伯来书4:12
a few moments I've heard lots of
片刻之后，我听到了很多
messages on Hebrews 4:12 but until
希伯来书4:12上的信息，但直到
recent years didn't hear much about the
最近几年没有听到太多关于
last phrase of Hebrews 4:12 Hebrews 4:12
希伯来书的最后一句4:12希伯来书4:12
is one of those wonderful passages of
是其中一段精彩的段落
scripture of why we're biblical
为何我们圣经的经文
counselors because the Word of God is
辅导员，因为上帝的话语是
living and active and sharper than any
生活， 活跃，比任何人都更敏锐
two-edged sword and because we believe
双刃剑，因为我们相信
the Word of God is alive we want to use
我们想要使用 上帝的话语
it to counsel people but notice what the
它为人们提供咨询， 但注意到了什么
rest of the verse says for the word of
这节经文的其余部分是用来说的
God is living and active and sharper
上帝活泼，活跃，更加敏锐
than any two-edged sword and piercing as
比任何双刃剑和穿孔更好
far as the division of soul and spirit
灵魂与精神的分裂
of both joints and marrow and it is able
关节和骨髓，它是能够的
to judge the thoughts and intentions of
判断的想法和意图
the heart now there are a lot of
心脏现在有很多
implications of that little phrase but
这个小词的含义但是
just think of one with me one of the
只想到一个跟我一起的人
really popular psychological theory
真正流行的心理理论
right now is that your inner person is
现在是你内心的人
passive and that you're really a victim
被动，你真的是受害者
and you're being acted upon by your
而你通过被采取行动的
environment and you really can't help
环境，你真的无法帮助
yourself because you're good on the
你自己，因为你是好上了
inside and it's really the environments
里面，它真的是环境
fault it's the cultures fault your
这是文化错误你的错
father didn't love you enough there's
父亲没有足够的爱你
just a whole slew of environmental
只是一大堆环境
theories about why you do what you do
关于你为什么做你做的事情的理论
scripture does not say though that your
经文不说虽然你的
inner person is passive
内心的人是被动的
according to this verse scripture says
根据这节经文所说
that our inner person is active here's
我们这个内心的人在这里很活跃
the way we would put it you have a
我们用它的方式你有一个
worshiping heart you have a heart that's
崇拜的心你有一颗心
very alive it has thoughts it has
非常活着它有它的想法
intentions another way to say it would
意图另一种方式说它会
be this if I do not learn to discipline
如果我不学会纪律，那就这样吧
my inner person I will just naturally
我内心的人， 我会很自然
live out the sinful desires of my heart
活出我心中的罪恶欲望
you can learn some good theology in
你可以学习一些好的神学
southern gospel songs every so often I'm
南方福音歌曲每隔一段时间我就是这样
from the South came here from Virginia
南方来自弗吉尼亚州
in like southern gospel music any amens
在南方福音音乐中任何amens
out there anybody likes southern gospel
在那里有人喜欢南方的福音
here's some theology I learned sin will
这是我学会了罪的一些神学
take you farther than you want to go and
带你去更远的比你想要去
keep you longer than you want to stay
让你比你想留下更久
living out my inner person I must learn
活出我的内心，我必须学习
how to discipline my inner person let's
如何训练我的内心让我们
think about the thoughts and intentions
想想想法和意图
of the heart first of all your heart has
心灵首先是你的心脏
thoughts don't bother to write this word
想不想写这个词
down but let me just give you a couple
我只想给你一两个
of definitions there about thoughts and
关于思想和思想的定义
through maysa is the word and it's much
通过maysa就是这个词而且它很多
more than concrete thought patterns like
不仅仅是具体的思维模式
the stuff that's just concretely going
那些具体的东西
through your mind right now this word
通过你的想法现在这个词
for heart the thoughts of your heart is
因为心灵的想法是
translated in Luke chapter 2 Mary kept
在路加第2章翻译玛丽保持
all these things and pondered them in
所有这些事情都在考虑他们
her heart the thoughts of her heart the
她心里想着她的心
ponderings
深思
it's not just the concrete things it's
它不仅仅是具体的东西
kind of those speculations the
那些猜测的那种
imagination fantasize what do you
想象力幻想你是什​​么
daydream about the thoughts of the heart
关于心灵的想法的白日梦
and then your heart has intentions this
然后你的心就有了这个意图
word has only used one other time and it
字只用一个其它的时间，它
has to do with the purposes the
与目的有关
attitudes the resolutions the designs of
态度决议的设计
the inner person and if you dwell on it
内心的人，如果你纠缠它
a little bit
一点点
you see how those two go together the
你看看这两个人是怎么走到一起的
thoughts and intentions of the heart
心灵的想法和意图
some summary thoughts here just to think
这里的一些总结思想只是为了思考
about this for a little bit more again
关于这一点再多一点
your heart is not passive according to
你的心不是被动的
the Bible my heart is active this is not
圣经我的心是活跃的， 这不是
what the secular psychologies believe I
世俗心理学认为我是什么
want to put a couple of quick quotes up
想要把一对夫妇的快速报价高达
here I'm gonna put some Abraham Maslow
我要放一些亚伯拉罕马斯洛
up here famous for his needs hierarchy
在这里以他的需求层次而闻名
and then I'm gonna put Carl Rogers up
然后我要去把罗杰斯起来
here they didn't believe in a sin nature
在这里，他们不相信罪性
for example Abraham Maslow as far as I
例如亚伯拉罕马斯洛，就我而言
know we just don't have any intrinsic
知道我们没有任何内在的
instincts for evil and you read that you
对邪恶的本能，你读到了你
go well where's the problem then he
那么问题就在那里
would say it's your environment the way
会说这是你的环境
your environment acts upon you if you
如果你，你的环境就会对你产生影响
think in terms of basic needs instincts
从基本需求本能的角度思考
at least at the outset are all good or
至少在开始时都是好
perhaps we should be technical about it
也许我们应该对此有所了解
and call them pre moral neither good nor
并称他们为道德既不善也不善
evil a little bit of Carl Rogers here
邪恶的卡尔罗杰斯在这里
for myself though I'm very aware of the
虽然我非常清楚这一点
incredible amount of destructive cruel
破坏性残酷的 令人难以置信的 大量
malevolent behavior in today's world
在当今世界的恶意行为
from the threats of war to the senseless
从战争的威胁到无知的
violence in the streets I do not find
在街上暴力我找不到
that this evil is inherent in human
这种邪恶是人类固有的
nature where does it come from then
自然它从何从那时
here's a couple more quotes I see
这是我看到的几个引用
members of the human species like
人类的成员就像
members of other species and by the way
其他物种的成员顺便说一下
if you're a species then what are you
如果你是一个物种，那么你是什​​么
you're an animal so there's a little bit
你是一个动物，所以有一点点
of evolutionary theory coming out you're
进化论的出现是你的
essentially constructive in your
本质上是建设性的
fundamental nature but damaged by their
基本性质但受其损害
experience he then went on to say
经历他接着说
experience leads me to believe that it
经验让我相信它
is cultural influences which are the
是文化的影响
major factor in our evil behaviors in
在我们的邪恶行为的主要因素
your notes you have some summary
你的笔记你有一些总结
thoughts about this idea of the heart
这个想法心脏的想法
let's just go through there I have for
就让我们经过那里我有
summary thoughts for you let me catch up
总结你的想法让我赶上来
to where you are
到你的位置
so for the unbeliever Jeremiah 17:9 the
所以对于不信的耶利米书17：9
heart is not fundamentally good we all
我们所有人的心并不是从根本上说好
know that we understand it bullet point
知道我们理解它的要点
- I'm trying to capture the idea that
- 我试图抓住这个想法
something different happens something
不同的东西发生了什么
different happens when you become a
当你成为一个不同的时候会发生
follower of Christ second Corinthians
基督第二哥林多人的追随者
5:17 says if any man is in Christ he's a
5:17 说如果有人在基督里，他就是一个人
new creation something there's a
新创造的东西有一个
fundamental change that happens and I'm
发生的根本变化，我
trying to capture though what is this
试图抓住这是什么
struggle though in the inner person so
虽然在内心的人中也是如此
the second bullet point says this as a
第二个要点是这个
Christian United with Christ amen that's
基督徒联合与基督阿门那是
Romans six we still struggle with unruly
罗马人六我们仍然在与不守规矩斗争
once sinful desires wrong drives I can
一旦罪欲错误的驱动器，我可以
be awful needy sometimes sinful passions
可怕的有时候是有罪的激情
misplaced expectations what reformed
错误的期望改革了什么
theology would call remnants in even
神学会把残余称为偶数
though we are a new creation in Christ
虽然我们是在基督里的新创造物
and the last sentence might be the most
最后一句可能是最多的
important it says sanctification still
重要的是它说成圣仍然存在
must happen in the heart the Lord wants
必须发生在主所希望的心中
to change me from the inside out third
让我从内到外改变 第三
bullet point I already made this point
要点我已经说明了这一点
so I'll skip over that and then let's go
所以我会跳过那个然后放手吧
to proverbs chapter 20 verse 5 you can
箴言20章5节 你可以
understand the heart but it takes work
了解内心，但它需要工作
look at proverbs chapter 20 verse 5 and
看一下箴言20章5节和
then we're about to make a crucial
那么我们即将成为关键
transition proverbs 20 verse 5 a plan in
过渡谚语20节5节计划
the heart of a man is like deep water
一个人的心就像深水
let's stop and think about that little
让我们停下来想想那个小
phrase for a little bit the plan in the
一点点的计划在
heart of a man is like deep water think
一个男人的心就像深水一样
of an old-fashioned well and get the
一个老式的井，得到了
picture in your mind of the little roof
小屋顶的图片
over it and it's got the bucket going
在它上面，它已经开始了
down in real well can you kind of
倒在真正的好你能种
picture that so we got the bucket going
我们得到了桶的图片
down into the well and the buckets going
进入水井，水桶进去
down and you're standing over the edge
下来，你站在边缘
of the well and you're watching the
你正在看井
bucket go down
桶下来
and after a few feet it disappears
几英尺后， 它消失了
because it's dark down there and it's
因为它在那里是黑暗的而且它是
going deep down in the water the plan in
深入了解水中的计划
the heart of a man is like deep water
一个人的心就像深水
it's it's hard am I ever always gonna I
我总是很难，我很难受
gonna ever Oh completely understand the
要完全理解哦
motives of my heart absolutely not but
我心中的动机绝对不是
can I understand the motives of my heart
我能理解我内心的动机吗？
yes a man of understanding draws it out
是的，一个理解的人把它拉出来
think of another synonym for
想另一个代名词的
understanding in the book of Proverbs
在箴言书中的理解
what would that word be wisdom so a part
那个词应该是智慧的一部分
of our dream in the biblical counseling
我们在圣经辅导中的梦想
movement is to teach people to learn to
运动是教人们学习的
be heart wise to start be a little more
要明智地开始多一点
tuned in to the motivations of your
调整你的动机
inner person especially because
内心的人特别是因为
scripture says the Lord wants us to love
经文说主要我们爱
him out of our inner person with our
他和我们一起离开了我的内心
heart soul mind and strength now let's
心灵的灵魂和力量现在让我们
make a crucial transition here and it's
在这里做一个至关重要的转变吧
gonna sound like a logical jump for just
听起来像是一个合乎逻辑的跳跃
a moment but I really believe that the
片刻，但我真的相信 ，
heart is our Worship Center just think
心脏是我们崇拜的中心只是觉得
of this verse and this isn't in your
这节经文， 这不是你的
notes but this will help get the idea
注意，但这将有助于理解
right off the bat here Matthew 6:21 our
马太福音6:21马上就下马了
Lord says something really important
主说了一些非常重要的事
where your treasure is there your heart
你的宝贝在哪里，你的心脏
will be also I do not believe and I
也将是我不相信和我
grappled with this for a long time is
长期以来一直在努力解决这个问题
the Lord saying that what you invest in
主说你投资的是什么
your heart will change your heart will
你的心会改变你的心意志
follow or is the Lord saying that what
跟随或是主说什么
you're investing in reveals where your
你在投资中揭示你的地方
heart already is after a lot of debate
心已经经过了很多争论
in my mind I came down on the second one
在我的脑海里，我倒下了第二个
that where your treasure is that's
你宝藏在那里
revealing where your heart is also now
揭示你的心脏现在也在哪里
let's just think about treasure for just
让我们想想宝只是
a moment to make the connection with
片刻，以促使与连接
worship the Old English word for worship
崇拜古英语单词进行崇拜
is anybody know worth-ship very good
是否有人知道值得运输非常好
the Old English word for worship is
崇拜的古英语单词是
worth ship why do we go to church on
值得一试为什么我们去教堂
Sunday morning because the Lord is
星期天早上因为主是
worth it we value him we treasure him
值得我们珍惜他，我们珍惜他
where your treasure is there your heart
你的宝贝在哪里，你的心脏
will be also we need to ask our counsel
我们也需要咨询我们的律师
'yes and start with ourselves so that
“是的，用我们自己，使启动
we're not hypocrites when we are
我们不是伪君子当我们
teaching our counsel 'yes what is it
教我们的律师'是的，是什么
that my inner person treasures well how
我内心的人很珍惜如何
can you tell when a person treasure
你能告诉一个人什么时候珍惜
something
某物
what are they investing in what are they
什么是他们投资于他们
talk about you can just go right through
谈谈你可以直接通过
the list and think about how to tell
列表并考虑如何分辨
what a person considers valuable and it
一个人认为有价值的东西
starts to bring together all the pieces
开始汇集所有的作品
of what it means to love the Lord your
爱你的意思是什么意思
God with all your heart soul mind and
神与你们所有的 心脏灵魂和心灵
strength I hope you're getting the idea
力量我希望你能得到这个想法
that when someone comes for counseling
当有人来咨询时
it's not just about I'm gonna help them
这不仅仅是因为我会帮助他们
with their depression I'm gonna help
他们的抑郁症我会帮助他们
them with their fear really what I'm
他们的恐惧真的是我的意思
going after because as Wayne so said it
追求因为韦恩如此说
so well in the last session it's about
它在上一届会议中表现得非常好
making disciples it might take a
使门徒可能需要一个
paradigm shift for this person of what
这个人的范式转移了什么
are you living for what do you value
你依靠什么重视你的生活吗？
what are you treasuring in your heart
你在心里珍惜什么？
it's really all about worship I believe
我相信这真是关于崇拜的全部
we were made to be worshipers of the
我们做成的崇拜者
true and living God lots of different
真实和活着的上帝有很多不同
verses we could go to for the sake of
经文我们可以去为求
time I'm just gonna quote that famous
时间我只是引用那个着名的
one right there first Corinthians 10:31
一个右边有哥林多前书10:31
adults don't miss the one little phrase
大人不要错过这个小短语
it's so important we often quote it this
它是如此重要， 我们经常引用它
way whether you eat or drink do all of
无论你是吃还是喝，都可以做到
the glory of God and that misses the
上帝的荣耀和错过了
significant phrase whether you eat or
重要的短语是否你吃或
drink or whatever you do do all to the
喝酒或任何你做的事情
glory of God if you think about that
上帝的荣耀，如果你考虑一下
diagram again that includes the heat of
图再次包括热量
my life which might be a traffic in LA
我的生活可能是洛杉矶的交通
how do I Drive in this traffic as an act
如何将此流量作为一种行为
of worship that's a tough one isn't it
崇拜是一个艰难的崇拜不是它
how do I Drive in this traffic as an act
如何将此流量作为一种行为
of worship so even though the
崇拜所以尽管如此
circumstance the heat in my life the
环境中我生命中的热量
pressure may not change on the left hand
压力可能不会改变在左手
side of the diagram the way I'm
我的方式是图的一面
responding from my inner person to the
从我内心的人回应
pressure in life
生活中的压力
change because instead of worshipping
改变因为而不是崇拜
what I was worshipping on the right hand
我在右边崇拜的是什么
side I'm learning to worship the Lord on
我正在学习崇拜主
the left hand side this is why back on
左手边这就是为什么重新开始
that diagram we had on the right hand
我们右边的那张图
side worship of idols john calvin put it
偶像崇拜约翰卡尔文说
this way the human heart is like a
这样人的心就像一个
cauldron constantly bubbling forth idols
大锅不断冒出偶像
it is just the tendency of humans to put
这只是人类的倾向
things in the place of God that's the
代替上帝的事物
next point in the outline it Romans 1:25
罗马书1:25的大纲中的下一个点
just so you can see it with your own
这样你就可以用自己的眼光看到它了
eyes turn there with me Romans 1:25 is a
眼睛转向我罗马书1:25是一个
basic verse about human nature Romans
关于人性罗马人的基本诗句
1:25 basic verse about humanity says
1:25 关于人性的基本经文说
this they exchanged the truth of God for
为此，他们将神的真理
a lie think the three trees diagram
一个谎言认为三棵树图
again got right-hand side left hand side
又站了右侧左手边
they exchanged the truth of God for a
他们将神的真实变为
lie and worshiped and served the
撒谎，敬拜和服务
creature rather than the Creator and
生物而不是造物主和生物
Paul can't help himself he's a worshiper
保罗无法帮助自己，他是一个崇拜者
so he says who is blessed forever Amen
所以他说永远祝福阿门的人
worshipping and serving the creature
崇拜和服务这个生物
rather than the Creator and I already
而不是造物主和我已经
have I already quoted Matthew 6:21 for
我已经引用马太福音6:21了
you where your treasure is there your
你对你的财宝在那里，你的
heart will be also
心脏也将
now I'm gonna put a picture up on the
现在我要把照片放在上面
screen and you're gonna go okay this is
屏幕，你会好起来的
a stretch but here you go why is it I
一段时间，但你在这里为什么是我
know what you're thinking now now he's
现在知道你现在在想什么
going to Medlen why is it that under the
要Medlen那为什么下
pressure of life think with me if you
如果你 ，生活的压力和我一起思考
would for a moment beloved why is it
会有一刻钟爱，为什么会这样
that under the pressure of life we think
在我们生活的压力下，我们认为
I need a good strong cup of Starbucks
我需要一杯好星巴克咖啡
rather than I need to go spend some time
而不是我需要花一些时间
with the Lord or this one I actually saw
与主或这一个我真的看到
this in a coffee shop and it was on a
这是在一家咖啡馆里，而且是在一家咖啡店
bumper sticker and here's what they had
保险杠贴纸，这是他们所拥有的
on the bumper sticker it said literally
在保险杠贴纸上它字面上说
that picture and then it said coffee is
那张照片然后它说咖啡是
God we worship and sir
上帝， 我们崇拜和先生
the creation rather than the Creator we
创造而不是创造者我们
were made for relationship with the
是为了与...建立关系
Creator we were made for something
创造者我们是为某事而做的
incredibly big we were made for him to
我们为他做的非常大
be as Psalm 18 says our rock our
正如诗篇18所说我们的摇滚乐
fortress our refuge but we have a
堡垒我们的避难所，但我们有一个
tendency to turn to things like that or
倾向于转向那种或类似的东西
maybe that let's think about this for a
也许让我们考虑一下这个
moment
时刻
you can't help but being religious if I
如果我，你会情不自禁
would say to you a man does his job
会对你说一个人做他的工作
religiously what does that mean and I've
这是什么意思和我的意思
done this with a lot of people all kinds
很多人都这样做了
of things come up it's this list a man
事情出现了，这个名单是男人
does his job religiously he studies it
他的工作是虔诚地研究它
he's dedicated to it he sings the praise
他致力于此，他唱赞美
of his company he likes to talk about it
他的公司 ， 他喜欢谈论它
and I'm using a religious word he
我用他的宗教词
witnesses about it he sacrifices for it
目击者为此牺牲了
he ascribes worth to it he gets excited
他认为值得，他很兴奋
about it it becomes his identity well
关于它它很好地成为他的身份
you know I've seen those kind of
你知道我见过那种
activities in a place like this i
在这样的一个 我 的地方活动
ministered for 14 years in Blacksburg
在布莱克斯堡服役 14 年
Virginia the home of the Virginia Tech
弗吉尼亚州弗吉尼亚理工大学的家
Hokies so that's a V T on the field
Hokies所以这是场上的VT
there and lots if you go back to that
有很多的，如果你回到那个
list I saw lots of those things going on
我看到很多这样的事情发生了
on Saturdays because humans are
星期六，因为人类
religious humans are looking for meaning
宗教人类正在寻找意义
and purpose in life what you should be
生活中的目标是什么
hearing right now as we are working with
我们正在合作，现在就听到
our counsel ease about fear and worry
我们的建议缓解恐惧和担忧
and anxiety is that it's really deeper
而焦虑是它真的更深
than that there's a worship problem
比那有一个崇拜问题
going on in the heart of my counsel Lee
继续在我的律师李 的心中
Augustine said it this way O Lord you
奥古斯丁说，这样主啊，你
made us for yourself and our hearts are
让我们自己和我们的心
restless until it finds its rest in you
不安， 直到它在你身上找到它的休息
John Piper put it this way the world has
John Piper用这种方式表达了这个世界
an inconsolable longing it tries to
一种令人无法忍受的渴望
satisfy the longing with scenic
满足对风景的渴望
vacations accomplishments of creativity
假期创造力的成就
stunning cinematic productions sexual
惊人的电影制作性
exploits sports extravagant
利用体育奢侈品
extravaganzas
十天
drugs ascetic rigors managerial
药物禁欲严谨管理
excellence but the longing remains what
卓越，但渴望仍然是什么
does this mean we're made for something
这是否意味着我们是为了某事而做的
bigger is what it means we're made for
更重要的是我们所做的意义
relationship with the Creator so what
与造物主的关系那么
are we doing with our counsel ease we're
我们是在做我们的忠告吗？
going deeper they came in thinking their
他们深入思考他们
problems this deep guess what their
这个问题深深猜到了什么
problems this deep because there's a
这个问题很深，因为有一个
worship problem going on in the person's
崇拜问题正在进行中
heart I'm going to skip ahead to the end
我要跳到最后
because we need to wrap this up but I
因为我们需要把它包起来但是我
have in your right at the very end some
在你在最后的一些 权
suggested words suggested themes and
建议的话建议主题和
here's what I'd like to challenge you to
这是我想要挑战你的
do take those hard questions there's 14
确实有14个问题
heart questions and go back through them
心脏问题，并通过他们回顾
and answer them for yourself take the
并回答他们为自己 取
three trees diagram and plug yourself
三棵树图和插头自己
into the pictures of the diagram what's
进入图表的图片是什么
causing the pressure in your life what's
造成生活压力的是什么
the fruit that's coming out on the right
从右边出来的水果
hand side the bad fruit and as you
手边的坏水果和你一样
answer those 14 heart questions ask
回答那14个心脏问题
yourself what are the patterns that I'm
你自己是什么样的模式
seeing about what could be going on in
看看可能会发生什么
my inner person and don't be surprised
我内心的人，不要感到惊讶
if it's some of those words wow I'm more
如果是这些话中的一些哇我会更多
of a comfort lover than I thought or
一个舒适的情人比我想象或
control is a big deal in my life we're
控制是 我生命中的 一件大事
keeping people happy is a really big
让人们快乐是一件非常重要的事情
deal in my life that's what the Bible
在我的生活中处理这就是圣经
would call the fear of man or
会叫对人类的恐惧
people-pleasing there's all kinds of
人们喜欢各种各样的
words and all you have to do is ask
所有你需要做的就是问
yourself what is it that I'm desiring
你自己想要的是什么
what is it that it seems like my life
它看起来像我的生活是什么？
revolves around all humans are religious
围绕着所有人都是宗教的
the human heart is like a cauldron
人的心就像一个大锅
constantly bubbling forth idols as John
像约翰一样不断冒出偶像
Calvin said counseling problems are not
凯文说咨询问题不是
just about the depression the fear the
只是关于抑郁的恐惧
worry or whatever the counseling
担心或无论什么辅导
presenting problem is in essence what
提出问题实质上是什么
we're saying is that biblical counseling
我们说的是圣经辅导
is trying to figure out the worship
正试图弄清楚崇拜
disorder in the person's life that is
这个人生活中的紊乱
the roots
根
of the inner person I hope this brief
内心的人我希望这个简短
presentation brings new meaning to the
演示带来了新的含义
idea of the Lord saying love the Lord
主的想法说爱主
your God with all your heart soul mind
你的上帝全心全意
and strength
和力量